{"data":[{"question":"In a new culture, many embarrassing situations occur ________ a misunderstanding.","a":"for","b":"of","c":"because of","d":"because","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Because of somebody\/something: used to say who or what causes something to happen or is the reason for something.\u00a0\n- Because + clause.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Neptune is an extremely cold planet, and ________.","a":"so does Uranus","b":"so has Uranus","c":"so is Uranus","d":"Uranus so","answer":"3","explain":"\n- So: used to show agreement with positive statements. \u00a0(so\u00a0+ auxiliary + subject pronoun)\u00a0\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"________ that gold was discovered at Sutter's Mill and that the California Gold Rush began.","a":"Because in 1848","b":"That in 1848","c":"In 1848 that it was","d":"It was in 1848","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Structure: It's ...that (to emphasize).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The job has no ________.","a":"prospectively","b":"prospects","c":"prospector","d":"prospective","answer":"2","explain":"\n- No: used as a determiner followed by a noun (= not any)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Frost occurs in valleys and on low grounds ________ on adjacent hills.","a":"more frequently as","b":"as frequently than","c":"more frequently than","d":"frequently than","answer":"3","explain":"\n- We use the comparative form of long adverb (frequently)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Mount Rushmore can be ________ from more than 100 kilometers away.","a":"see","b":"saw","c":"been seen","d":"seen","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Passive voice with modal verb (can\/could\/ will...): can\/could\/ will...+ be +PP.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"I'd like you ________ my family this weekend.","a":"meet","b":"to meet","c":"meeting","d":"to meeting","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Would like somebody to do sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Cold objects emit ________ hot objects.","a":"fewer than infrared rays as","b":"fewer infrared rays than","c":"fewer infrared rays as","d":"as fewer infrared rays","answer":"2","explain":"\n- We use the comparative form of short adverb (few)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Mr. Green, along with his friends, ________ arriving here tonight.","a":"is","b":"are","c":"was","d":"were","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Mr Green (subject): is singular","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The statement will be spoken just one time; therefore, you must listen very ________ in order to understand what the speaker has said.","a":"carefully","b":"careful","c":"care","d":"careless","answer":"1","explain":"\n- We use an adverb(carefully) after a verb (listen)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"}]}